So far, you've imported modules with import followed by the module name,
到目前为止 你已经学会导入模块 方法是输入 import 然后是模块名称
which makes all the classes of objects and
这样就可以用点记法
functions of that module available via.notation.
使用该模块中的所有对象和模块
There are some other variance of importing that are useful in other situations.
还有适合其他情形的一些其他导入方式
You can import an individual function or class from a module like this,
你可以像这样从模块中导入单个函数或类
from, the module name,
输入 from 模块名称
import, the object name.
import 对象名称
This gives access only to defaultdict from the collections module.
这样只能访问 collections 模块中的 defaultdict
Defaultdict will be accessible with its own name without the module name before it.
可以直接使用 defaultdict 的名称访问它 无需在前面加上模块名称
Trying to access collections or even calling
尝试访问 collections
collections.defaultdict will give a name error.
甚至调用 collections.defaultdict() 将出现 NameError
Importing individual objects from a module means you only take
从模块中导入单个对象意味着只获取所需的对象
what you need and you don't need to use.notation to access them.
并且不需要使用点记法来访问这些对象
You can import multiple individual objects from a module by separating them with commas.
你可以导入某个模块的多个对象 用英文逗号分隔即可
This technique is very common when importing pieces from large libraries.
导入大型库的多个对象时 经常会用到这种技巧
And as you saw before,
正如你之前所看到的
you can import a module and give it a different,
可以导入一个模块并设定一个不同的名称
usually shorter name, like this.
通常更简短 就像这样
If the name of a module is particularly long or
如果模块名称非常长
if there's a clash with something with the same or similar name,
或者与相同或相似的名称有冲突
renaming the module like this can be helpful.
像这样重命名模块很有用
Check code examples in the documentation as these will often
请参阅文档中的代码示例
include a standard abbreviation if one is used for this module.
因为这些代码经常包含标准缩写（如果该模块有缩写的话）
Using an abbreviation that is consistent with others will make your code more readable.
使用与他人的缩写保持一致的缩写将使你的代码更容易读懂
For example, the standard abbreviation for the multiprocessing module is MP.
例如 multiprocessing 模块的标准缩写是 mp
You can combine the previous two pieces of syntax to
你可以结合使用之前的两种语法
input an item from a module and change its name.
输入某个模块中的某项并更改其名称
Again, you'll be able to access
同样 你将只能使用新指定的名称
only that individual item directly with its newly specified name.
直接访问该项目
No.notation is needed.
不需要点记法
This can be useful if you have multiple objects
如果你的命名空间内有多个名称相似
with similar names from different packages in your namespace.
来自不同软件包的对象 这样会很方便
For example, perhaps you want a CSV reader and JSON reader.
例如 或许你需要一个 CSV 阅读器和一个 JSON 阅读器
You could import them from their respective modules and give them descriptive names.
你可以从各自的模块中导入这两个阅读器 并设定描述性名称
Another way of importing that you may see in
你可能在其他人的代码中见过另一种导入方式
other people's code but that you should not use is this.
但是你不能使用这种方式
Using this asterisk will import every object from
使用星号将单独导入模块中的每个对象
a module individually and allow you to access each of them directly via its name.
并且使你能够通过对象名称直接访问每个对象
The real problem with this is that modules may contain many objects,
但真正的问题是模块可能包含很多对象
each of which has a name.
每个对象都有一个名称
Including all these names may overwrite or maybe
包含所有这些名称可能会替换你在程序中使用的其他名称
overwritten by other names you're using in your program.
或被这些名称替换
Import star also makes it impossible for
import * 使协作者无法找到
collaborators to find where an important object was defined.
导入对象的定义位置
A reader can search for a definition of a function and not find it and
阅读器可以搜索函数定义并找到定义
they won't know which import star statement introduced a function.
但是不知道哪个 import * 语句引入了函数
These problems can lead to a lot of confusion.
这些问题会让人很困惑
Do not use from module name import asterisk.
请勿使用“from 模块名称 import *”语句
If you really want to use all the objects from the Random module,
如果你的确想要使用 random 模块中的所有对象
use the standard import random instead and access each of the objects with the.notation.
请使用标准的 import random 语句 并用点记法访问每个对象